[{"question": " here you go.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  say rachel, i was wondering if you\u0092d like to go to a movie with me sometime. as my lover! nnnsch, to out there. maybe you\u0092d just like to ah, get something to eat with me sometime? as my lover.", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " hi! all right, let\u0092s go shoppin\u0092!!", "answer": " um, y'know, before we go ah, there\u0092s something i need to say.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " oh, okay.", "answer": " i\u0092ve kinda of had this ah, this crush on you.  but since you were with ross, i-i didn\u0092t do anything about it. but, now that you\u0092re not, i\u0092d really like to ask you out sometime. so-so that\u0092s-that\u0092s what i\u0092m doing, now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " ...so y'know, that\u0092s why, within a few years, that voice recognition is gonna be pretty much standard on any computer you buy. y'know, so you could be like-like, \u0091wash my car.\u0092 \u0091clean my room.\u0092 it\u0092s not gonna be able to do any of those things, but it\u0092ll understand what you\u0092re saying.", "answer": " oh, this is so great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " yeah, it was.", "answer": " all right then.  bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " hello, people who do not live here.", "answer": " hi! hello!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " i gave you a key for emergencies!", "answer": " we were out of doritos.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey, how\u0092d the date go with mr. millionaire?", "answer": " mr. millionaire, new from snooty playthings! third wife sold separately.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " he\u0092s great! i mean we have such a good time together! he\u0092s so funny, and sooo sweet, and i\u0092m not attracted to him at all!!", "answer": " still?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " noo!! it\u0092s driving me crazy. i mean every other way he\u0092s like the perfect guy, he has everything. plus! he actually has everything.", "answer": " life-sized imperial storm troopers from sharper image?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " two.", "answer": " wow!! can joey and i put them on and fight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i guess he musta gotten the part in that play. monica and phoebe: oh.", "answer": " yeah, either that, or gloria estefan was right, eventually, the rhythm is going to get you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " joe. how\u0092s it going?", "answer": " good.  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " oh, so you\u0092re playing adrienne, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " yes. are you one of the retarded cousins?", "answer": " oh, no. ah, i playing your husband, victor. i\u0092m joey tribianni.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " so the ah, play\u0092s pretty great, huh?", "answer": " oh, yeah. i love jennifer van murray\u0092s work. she\u0092s so brilliantly incisive when it comes to deconstructing the psyche of the american middle class.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " oh, forget about it. she rocks!", "answer": " where do i know you from?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " dr. drake remoray. days of our lives. voted most datable neurosurgeon by teen beat.", "answer": " no, that\u0092s not it. so, you\u0092re a soap actor? well this must be pretty exciting for you to be in a real play, hmm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " hey, i\u0092ve done plays before. i\u0092m a serious actor.", "answer": " that info-mercial! for the milk carton spout thing! you\u0092re-you\u0092re-you\u0092re the guy that doesn\u0092t know how to pour milk!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " see, i actually can pour milk, but i got you believing that i couldn\u0092t. now, see, that\u0092s acting.", "answer": " right, at the end, you choked on a cookie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " wow! i cannot believe mark asked you out.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " what, so what are you gonna tell him?", "answer": " well, i told him i would think about it, but i\u0092m gonna tell him no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " i mean i think i\u0092d say no to anybody right now.  oh, but it was so strange. i mean i\u0092m standing there with this charming, cute guy, who\u0092s asking me to go out with him, which i\u0092m allowed to do, and i felt guilty. y'know, like i\u0092d be cheating on ross or something.", "answer": " wow. so, okay, maybe that means that, you\u0092re not over ross yet and you have issues with your father.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i don\u0092t have any issues with my father.", "answer": " okay, so it\u0092s probably just the ross thing then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i hate this woman!! i hate her! she told everyone in the company about that info-mercial, and now they all keep asking me to open their drinks. okay, and whenever i can\u0092t do it, they\u0092re all like-like laughing at me.", "answer": "  hello. chandler and joey: hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " so rachel called. wants to see me. going over in a minute.", "answer": " wow, what-what do you think she wants?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " well, maybe the crazy fog has lifted and she realises that life without me.... a-sucks.", "answer": " it\u0092s possible. you are very loveable, i\u0092d miss you if i broke up with you.  i was just trying to be supportive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " then be supportive like a guy.", "answer": "  if i broke up with you, i\u0092d miss you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " you ah, wanted to see me?", "answer": " yeah. ahh, here\u0092s a box of your stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " oh, y'know, it\u0092s just like hats, and a shirt, and cd\u0092s, just sort of stuff that you\u0092ve left here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " what are you doing? are you trying to hurt me? or something?", "answer": " no. ross, it, it just seems that y'know it\u0092s time we-we y'know, move on. i mean, i mean don\u0092t\u0092 you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yes, i do.", "answer": " good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yeah, i-i really do.  hey! this-this was a gift?!", "answer": " ross, you got that for free from the museum gift shop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " it\u0092s still a gift! i got it from the gift shop!", "answer": " okay, all right, give me the mug! i\u0092ll keep the mug.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " no!! y'know-y'know don\u0092t do me any favours. in fact, where, where\u0092s the rest of my stuff?! huh? like-like my umm,  hey, this book is mine!! and-and-and, and that t-shirt you sleep in? i\u0092d like that back too. yes, i do.", "answer": " you know how much i love that t-shirt! you never even where that t-shirt!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " i\u0092m just trying to help you, move on.", "answer": " oh, you are a petty man. you are a petty, petty....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " petty...", "answer": " petty...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " petty...", "answer": " petty...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " petty...", "answer": " small...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " you are so just doing this out of spite.", "answer": " awwwahuh, no, no, no!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " huh?", "answer": " i\u0092m-i\u0092m gonna wear this all the time! i love this shirt!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " you have not worn that t-shirt since you were 15!! it doesn\u0092t even fit you anymore!", "answer": " oh, yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  yeah-yeah-yeah!!", "answer": " oh-oh, okay, okay!  if you don\u0092t mind i\u0092m gonna the rest of my stuff, and relax, in my favourite shirt.  you have a pleasant evening.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " and you\u0092re our age. you\u0092re our age.", "answer": " y'know what, you should like, you should buy a state and then just name it after yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " what like pete dakota?", "answer": " yeah, or, or, or, mississ-pete.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " oh, oh, i got it! pete-chicago.", "answer": " that\u0092s not a state joe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " oh, and mississ-pete is?", "answer": " i got to go, so ah, i\u0092ll see you guys later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " you\u0092re our age!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  so ah, we on for tomorrow?", "answer": " absolutely!  now get out of here you!!   okay, i\u0092m running out of places i can touch him! look, is there something wrong with me? i mean why am i only attracted to guys where there\u0092s no future? either they\u0092re too old, or they\u0092re too young, and then there\u0092s pete who\u0092s-who\u0092s crazy about me, and who\u0092s absolutely perfect for me, and there\u0092s like zip going on! i mean, seriously, does it sound like something\u0092s wrong with me?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " happy?! is that what i\u0092m supposed to be vic? happy?", "answer": " well, why don\u0092t you tell me what you\u0092re supposed to be! huh? because i sure as hell can\u0092t figure it out! i talk to you and nothin\u0092. you look at me, and it\u0092s nothin\u0092.  nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " tasty! i\u0092m really starting to feel like you guys have a history, it\u0092s-it\u0092s nice.", "answer": " i have a question about this scene.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " yes?", "answer": " well, i don\u0092t understand why adrienne\u0092s attracted to victor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " peel the onion. first of all, he\u0092s good looking.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i think my character\u0092s gonna need a little bit more of reason than that.", "answer": " oh, hey, how about this one. ah, it\u0092s says so in the script! y'know ah, i-i don\u0092t know why my character likes you either, i mean it says in the script here that you\u0092re a bitch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " it doesn\u0092t say that in the script.", "answer": " it does in mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " i can blow dry it. i can put gel on it. it doesn\u0092t matter, i still wind up with this little  cowlicky thing on the middle part of my head. it\u0092s so annoying. does it bug you?", "answer": " you bug me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " ross! you gotta stop! okay?! you can\u0092t just stare through the peep hole for three hours! you\u0092re gonna get peep eye!", "answer": " i knew it! i knew it! i always knew she liked him! y'know, she\u0092d say no, but here we are! right? we just broke up, first thing she does!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " you didn\u0092t just break up.", "answer": " hey, it\u0092s been like three weeks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " you slept with somebody three hours after you thought you broke up. i mean bullets have left guns slower!", "answer": " here they come, here they come. oh-ho, if she kisses him goodnight, i\u0092m gonna kill myself, i swear. i can\u0092t, i can\u0092t watch this.  come on, date over! date over! uh-oh, here we go, she\u0092s going in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " she\u0092s going in. wait! he\u0092s going in! he\u0092s going in!! the door\u0092s closed! i, i can\u0092t see anything but the door closed!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " and the inventor of the door rests happily in his grave.", "answer": " okay, i have to do something. i mean, i have, i have to stop it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " stop what?!", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, but i ah, i have the feeling that my being there will do it. i\u0092ll go over and i will borrow something. juice!! i need juice!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no!! you can\u0092t!!", "answer": " look, they must be stopped!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i am your friend, and i am not gonna let you do this!!  you are surprisingly strong!", "answer": " i need juice! people need juice!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " look man!", "answer": " people need juice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " juice, i need...", "answer": " she\u0092s moving on! okay, if it\u0092s not this guy, it\u0092s gonna be somebody else! and unless you\u0092re thinking about subletting my peep hole, you are going to have to get used to the fact that the relationship is over! okay, man? it\u0092s over.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " yeah, okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " it\u0092s just i miss her so much.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " why do all you\u0092re coffee mugs have numbers on the bottom?", "answer": " oh. that\u0092s so monica can keep track. that way if one on them is missing, she can be like, \u0091where\u0092s number 27?!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " y'know what?", "answer": " no. and i don\u0092t think i\u0092m gonna want to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " i can\u0092t do this.", "answer": " yep. yep, that\u0092s what i didn\u0092t want to know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " well, oh, mark, i\u0092m doing this for the wrong reasons, y'know? i\u0092m just doing it to get back at ross. i\u0092m sorry, it\u0092s not very fair to you.", "answer": " ahh! fair, schmair! y'know? look, if you want to get back at ross, i am here for you. really? no-no, i say-i say, i say we get back at him right on this couch. right here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " oh god. i\u0092m sorry about this.", "answer": " that\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " you sure?", "answer": " yeah. i can just go home and get back at him by myself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " ...has become the penicillin of the twenty-first century. and so today, this hospital is about to take major steps toward leading that revolution. it is truly ironic, on one hand consider the size...", "answer": "  hey, can i ask you something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " sure.", "answer": " where are we?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": "  well, with all these doctors and nurses, i\u0092m gonna say, midget rodeo.", "answer": " just tell me the truth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " okay. umm, y'know, i don\u0092t think, i don\u0092t think i told you this, but umm, i just got out of a really serious relationship.", "answer": " oh, yeah. wasn\u0092t that like a year ago?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " so i did tell you. okay, y'know, that really isn\u0092t the thing. umm, the thing is that, right now i\u0092m just in a place in my life where i need to focus on me. y'know what i mean?", "answer": " oh, yeah. i know that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " i so wanna be attracted to you.", "answer": " but you\u0092re not. okay, good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " y'know what, don\u0092t be. this is not, don\u0092t be, \u0091cause it\u0092s not so bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " it\u0092s not?", "answer": " i know i\u0092m no john bon jovi,  or someone who find attractive, i\u0092m just, i think, y'know, that you might end up feeling differently.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " well, um, look i-i don\u0092t want this to come our wrong, but ah, you seem awfully confident for a guy i just told i wasn\u0092t attracted too.", "answer": " yeah, stupidly charming isn\u0092t\u0092 it? well listen let\u0092s, you wanna get something to eat? \u0091cause this place is kinda depressing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " and the man who made all this possible... mr. peter becker.", "answer": "  one second.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  i wasn\u0092t doing anything.  uh-oh, what did she do now?", "answer": " just because she went to yale drama, she thinks she\u0092s like the greatest actress since, since, sliced bread!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " ah, sliced bread, a wonderful lady macbeth.", "answer": " god, i just, i hate her! i hate her!! with her, \u0091oh, i\u0092m so talented.\u0092 and \u0091oh, i\u0092m so pretty,\u0092 and \u0091ooh, i smell so good.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i think somebody has a crush on somebody.", "answer": " hey, chandler, can we please stay focused on my problem here?! y'know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " i\u0092m talking about you. you big, big freak.", "answer": " oh.  ohh. ohh, you\u0092re out of your mind.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " hey, you have nothing but talk about her for the last 48 hours! if you were in a school yard you\u0092d be pulling her pigtails and pushing her down now!", "answer": " oh, yeah?! then how come i keep thinking about her in all these sexual scenarios and stuff huh?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " happy?! is that what i\u0092m supposed to be vic? happy?", "answer": " well, why don\u0092t you tell me what you\u0092re supposed to be! huh? because i sure as hell can\u0092t figure it out! i talk to you and it\u0092s nothin\u0092. you look at me, and nothin\u0092.  nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " you guys make me fly! high! okay, we\u0092re gonna pick it up here, tomorrow.", "answer": " well, that was ah...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " better?", "answer": " yeah! yeah, it was definitely an improvement. g\u0092night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " ah, kate?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " you ah, you forgot your shoes.", "answer": "  i\u0092m probably gonna need those. huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " hey, listen you ah....", "answer": " hmm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " ...feel like getting a cup of coffee?", "answer": " umm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  kate?", "answer": " yep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " you ready to go?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " so umm, i\u0092ll see you tomorrow, huh?", "answer": " yeah, yeah sure, goodnight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  hey!  why isn\u0092t it spiderman? y\u0092know like goldman, silverman...", "answer": " \u0091cause it\u0092s-it\u0092s not his last name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " it isn\u0092t?", "answer": " no, it\u0092s not like, like phil spiderman. he\u0092s a spider, man. y'know like ah, like goldman is a last name, but there\u0092s no gold man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " oh, okay. there should be gold man!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " hey, rach, how was work?", "answer": " oh, great. although i did sit down where there wasn\u0092t a chair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " by the way, ross dropped by a box of your stuff.", "answer": " oh, well, i guess i had that one coming. i\u0092m just gonna throw it out, it\u0092s probably just a bunch of shampoo and...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " something wrong?", "answer": "  no. nothing.  closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " so, ahh, what kind of powers would gold man have?", "answer": " okay well, he would turn things to gold.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " what about things that are already gold?", "answer": " ahh, his work is done.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " okay, let\u0092s play my game now.", "answer": " okay. all right you yellow-bellied-lilly-livered-draw!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}]